Stomp the Yard 2: Homecoming is a drama, music film directed by Rob Hardy.
Chance Harris looks to find a balance between his school, work, relationships and opportunity to perform at
the nationally televised step competition during homecoming weekend at Truth University.
Brenda, played by Kiely Williams.
Nikki, played by Tika Sumpter.
Taz, played by Stephen 'tWitch' Boss.
Chance Harris, played by Collins Pennie.
DJ Williams, played by Columbus Short.
Terry, played by Keith David.
Stomp the Yard: Homecoming is a 2010 American dance drama film
directed by Rob Hardy and produced by Will Packer.
It is the sequel to the 2007 American dance drama film  Stomp the Yard.
The film was released direct-to-video on September 21, 2010.
Cast members include Collins Pennie, Pooch Hall, Jasmine
Guy, David Banner, Terrence J and Keith David.
The tone is emotional.